A Guide to the Office of the Dean of Students Office Administrative Files, 1986-2001
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Office of the Dean of Students Office Administrative Files 1986-2001
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-18/2/1.001
This collection consists of 7,000 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 2000 October 17.
Scope and Content Information
Topical files of V. Shamim Sisson, Associate Dean of Students; and, F. Aaron Laushway and Michelle A. Samuels, Assistant Deans of Students.
Organization
Series I: Associate Dean of Students, Shamin Sisson Boxes 1-7
Series II: Assistant Dean of Students, Aaron Laushway Boxes 8-13
Series III: Assistant Dean of Students, Michelle Samuels Boxes 14-17
Series IV: Restricted Files Box 18
Contents List
- Series I: Associate Dean of Student, Shamin Sisson
  - Athletic Advisory Subcommittee 1995-1998 (Box 1)
  - Contact List - Student Government Organizations and Media 1995, 1997, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Student Council Miscellaneous Information 1999 (Box 1)
  - U.Va. Exit Interviews 1991-1993 (Box 1)
  - U.Va. Exit Interviews 1986-1990 (Box 1)
  - Family Weekend Updates 1998 (Box 1)
  - Family Weekend Brochure 1998 (Box 1)
  - Family Weekend (3 folders) 1998 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous Pamphlets (2 folders) 1998-1999 (Box 2)
  - Family Weekend (2 folders) 1999 (Box 2)
  - Family Weekend Reservations 1999 (Box 2)
  - Family Weekend Brochure (2 folders) 1999 (Box 2)
  - Family Weekend Phonemail 1998 (Box 2)
  - First Year Seminar 1998-1999 (Box 2)
  - Hazing 1993 (Box 2)
  - Honor System Study 1990-1991 (Box 3)
  - Jefferson Society Report 1993 (Box 3)
  - Police Luncheon; Leadership 2000 1997 (Box 3)
  - Leadership 2000 (3 folders) 1998 (Box 3)
  - Leadership 2000 Housing 1997-1998 (Box 3)
  - Housing Agreements 1998 (Box 3)
  - Leadership 2000 Originals 1998 (Box 3)
  - Leadership 2000 Evaluations 1998 (Box 3)
  - Longitudinal Study 1996 (Box 3)
  - Mediation Intern 1996-1997 (Box 4)
  - Mediation (4 Folders) 1996-1997 (Box 4)
  - NASPA/SACSA Mid-Managers' Institute 1996-1998 (Box 4)
  - Newcomb Hall Grand Re-Opening 1996-1997 (Box 4)
  - ODOS Assessment: General (2 folders) 1997-1998 (Box 4)
  - Assessment and Student Development 1998 (Box 4)
  - ODOS Assessment: Questionnaires; Form W-87; SDTLI
  - Orientation 1996-1998 (Box 5)
  - Parent's Orientation 1996-1998 (Box 5)
  - Phi Eta Sigma (2 folders) 1997-1999 (Box 5)
  - Self-Study-Non-traditional Students and Off-grounds Programs Committee 1994-1995 (Box 5)
  - Women's Leadership Development Program 1997-1998 (Box 5)
  - Women's Leadership Development Nominations 1997 (Box 6)
  - Women's Leadership Development Program Registrations 1997-1998 (Box 6)
  - Women's Leadership Development Program Committee Applications 1997 (Box 6)
  - Women's Leadership Development Program Applications 1998 (Box 6)
  - Women's Leadership Development Program Mentors/Mentees 1997-1998 (Box 6)
  - Session I 1998 (Box 6)
  - Session II 1998 (Box 6)
  - Final Dinner 1998 (Box 6)
  - Surveys 1998 (Box 6)
  - Brochures 1998-1999 (Box 6)
  - Women's Leadership Development Program Form Letters and Originals 1998 (Box 6)
  - Women's Leadership Development Program 1998-1999 (Box 6)
  - Potential Women's Leadership Development Committee Members 1998-1999 (Box 6)
  - Women's Leadership Development Program Registration 1998 (Box 6)
  - Mentorship Applications 1999 (Box 7)
  - Women's Leadership Development Mentor Survey 1999 (Box 7)
  - Women's Leadership Development Program Session 1 1999 (Box 7)
  - Women's Leadership Development Program Session 2 1999 (Box 7)
  - Women's Leadership Development Program Final Dinner 1999 (Box 7)
  - Women's Leadership Development Program 1999 (Box 7)
  - Women's Center Council Program Advisory Committee 1998 (Box 7)
- Series II: Assistant Dean of Students, Aaron Laushway
  - Alpha Chi Omega 1996-1998 (Box 8)
  - Alpha Delta Phi 1996-1998 (Box 8)
  - Alpha Delta Pi 1996-1998 (Box 8)
  - Alpha Epsilon Pi 1996-1998 (Box 8)
  - Alpha Gamma Delta 1990-1992 (Box 8)
  - Alpha Omicron Pi 1993-1995 (Box 8)
  - Alpha Phi 1996-1998 (Box 8)
  - Alpha Tau Omega 1996-1998 (Box 8)
  - Beta Theta Pi 1996-1998 (Box 8)
  - Chi Phi 1996-1998 (Box 8)
  - Chi Psi 1996-1998 (Box 8)
  - Delta Delta Delta 1996-1998 (Box 8)
  - Delta Gamma 1996-1998 (Box 8)
  - Delta Kappa Epsilon 1996-1998 (Box 8)
  - Delta Sigma Phi 1996-1998 (Box 8)
  - Delta Sigma Theta 1996-1998 (Box 8)
  - Delta Tau Delta 1996-1998 (Box 8)
  - Delta Upsilon 1996-1998 (Box 8)
  - Gamma Phi 1996-1998 (Box 9)
  - Kappa Alpha 1996-1998 (Box 9)
  - Kappa Alpha Psi 1996-1998 (Box 9)
  - Kappa Kappa Gamma 1996-1998 (Box 9)
  - Kappa Sigma 1996-1998 (Box 9)
  - Omega Psi Phi 1996-1998 (Box 9)
  - Phi Delta Theta 1996-1998 (Box 9)
  - Phi Gamma Delta 1996-1998 (Box 9)
  - Phi Kappa Psi 1996-1998 (Box 9)
  - Phi Kappa Sigma 1996-1998 (Box 9)
  - Phi Sigma Kappa 1996-1998 (Box 9)
  - Pi Beta Phi 1996-1998 (Box 9)
  - Phi Mu (Restricted) 1996-1998 (Box 9)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha 1996-1998 (Box 10)
  - Pi Kappa Phi 1996-1998 (Box 10)
  - Pi Lambda Phi 1996-1998 (Box 10)
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon 1996-1998 (Box 10)
  - Sigma Alpha Mu 1996-1998 (Box 10)
  - Sigma Chi 1996-1998 (Box 10)
  - Sigma Kappa 1996-1998 (Box 10)
  - Sigma Nu 1996-1998 (Box 10)
  - Sigma Phi 1996-1998 (Box 10)
  - Sigma Phi Epsilon 1996-1998 (Box 10)
  - Sigma Pi 1996-1998 (Box 10)
  - Delta Psi; St. Anthony's Hall 1996-1998 (Box 11)
  - Theta Chi 1996-1998 (Box 11)
  - Theta Delta Chi 1996-1998 (Box 11)
  - Zeta Beta Nu 1996-1998 (Box 11)
  - Zeta Tau Alpha 1996-1998 (Box 11)
  - Zeta Psi 1996-1998 (Box 11)
  - CIO Update 1999-2001 (Box 12)
  - Association of Fraternity Advisors CIO Attachment B 1990-1996 (Box 12)
  - Graduate Assistant 1996-1997 (Box 12)
  - Alison S. (Graduate Assistant) 1995-1996 (Box 12)
  - Fraternity Council (IFC) Miscellaneous 1997 (Box 12)
  - F. Aaron Laushway's E-mails 1997-1999 (Box 12)
  - Greek Coordinating Committee 1997-1998 (Box 12)
  - Greek Coordinating Committee 1996-1997 (Box 12)
  - Activities 1997 (Box 13)
  - Attorney General's Visit 1998 (Box 13)
  - Capital Campaign 1994 (Box 13)
  - Casteen 1993 (Box 13)
  - Cavalier Daily 1999 (Box 13)
  - Charlottesville Ten Miler 1996 (Box 13)
  - University Correspondences 1997 (Box 13)
  - Educational Videos n.d. (Box 13)
  - Facilities Coordinator 1994-1999 (Box 13)
  - Financial Aid 1991 (Box 13)
  - Graduate Practicum 1993-1995 (Box 13)
  - Graduate Students 1992 (Box 13)
  - Leadership 2000 1997 (Box 13)
  - Leadership 2000 1996 (Box 13)
  - National Clearinghouse Leadership Program 1996 (Box 13)
  - New President Meeting 1997 (Box 13)
  - Fraternity Promotion 1996 (Box 13)
  - Sarah Curtis-Fawley and Fraternities n.d. (Box 13)
  - Social Marketing 1997 (Box 13)
  - Student Orientation Review Committee 1997 (Box 13)
- Series III: Assistant Dean of Students, Michelle Samuels
  - African American Leadership 1996-1997 (Box 14)
  - African American Leadership Association Correspondence 1998 (Box 14)
  - African American Leadership Association 1997-1998 (Box 14)
  - African American Leadership Conference Brochures 1995 (Box 14)
  - African American Leadership Evaluations 1998 (Box 14)
  - Third Local High School's Leadership Conference 1998 (Box 14)
  - Third Leadership Conference Evaluations 1998 (Box 14)
  - Asian American Student Survey 1992 (Box 14)
  - Asian Student Survey 1993 (Box 14)
  - Black Women's Groups: "In the Company of My Sisters" 1997 (Box 14)
  - Sisterhood Outreach 1997-1998 (Box 14)
  - Sista Social 1997-1998 (Box 14)
  - Culture Group Curriculum Initiatives 1999 (Box 14)
  - Cultural Programming Board 1999-2000 (Box 14)
  - Cultural, Religious Student Organizations and Support Officers 1999 (Box 14)
  - Cultural Support Team 1998-1999 (Box 14)
  - First Year Council 1999-2000 (Box 14)
  - First Year Focus Facilitators 1996 (Box 15)
  - First Year Focus Program Evaluations 1996 (Box 15)
  - First Year Coffee House 1998 (Box 15)
  - First Year Focus 1996 (Box 15)
  - First Year Focus Program Evaluations Results 1996 (Box 15)
  - Fall Convocation 1997 (Box 15)
  - Hispanic/Latino Affairs 1998-1999 (Box 15)
  - List of Hispanic/Latino Students and Parents 1998 (Box 15)
  - LGB Leadership Seminar 1994-1995 (Box 15)
  - Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, and Transgendered 1998-1999 (Box 15)
  - Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual Issues 1993-1994 (Box 15)
  - Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, Transgendered Union at U. Va. 1998 (Box 15)
  - Multi-Cultural Education 1997 (Box 15)
  - Multi-Cultural Facilitators Consulting Process 1997 (Box 15)
  - Multi-Cultural Task Force 1996-1997 (Box 15)
  - Multi-Culturalism/Diversity Definitions 1997 (Box 15)
  - Multi-Culturalism Facilitators Materials 1995 (Box 16)
  - First Year Focus Facilitators Applications 1995 (Box 16)
  - Multi-Culturalism Presenters 1995-1996 (Box 16)
  - Oasis 1998 (Box 16)
  - Oasis 1999 (Box 16)
  - Oasis Participants 1997 (Box 16)
  - Facilities Orientation 1997 (Box 16)
  - Facilities Orientation Evaluations 1998 (Box 16)
  - Summer Orientation Sessions 1999 (Box 16)
  - Orientation Director's Manual 1996 (Box 16)
  - Orientation Panel for Parents 1998 (Box 16)
  - Orientation Planning (2 folders) 1998 (Box 16)
  - Orientation Schedules (Orders) 1998 (Box 17)
  - Orientation Task Force 1998 (Box 17)
  - Resident Staff Orientation 1999 (Box 17)
  - Rooms for Orientation 1998 (Box 17)
  - Supplemental Brochure 1998 (Box 17)
  - Tentative Orientation Brochures 1999 (Box 17)
  - President's Convocation 1997 (Box 17)
  - President's Convocation 1998 (Box 17)
  - Peace and Solidarity Week 1996 (Box 17)
- Series IV: Restricted Files (Box 18)